[music]
The lighting is totally
rubbish.
Yes, you just have to turn around.
Yes, then just do it.
You know, you always say you just have to
, you just have to.  But
you know, actions speak louder than words,
and with that, hello.  Huh?
Everything's included, right?  You cut
it out.  I know you know it yourself.
You don't have anyone.
Hello.   Yes
.  Hey, [laughter] we're in
Portugal, the
Portuguese,
and
[laughter] they could have done
better.  What's going on here?
Welcome to this new vlog.  I
hope you are all well.  Jana hopes so
too.  We are doing very well because we are
in Portugal.  We're in Lagos, we're having lots of
fun.  We have been here
since yesterday
and
we are hungry, and therefore the
hotel breakfast is not good enough.
Oh my God, that's not true at all
.  You say it as if I just
want fun.
I just don't feel like a
normal hotel breakfast today;
I want to have some fun in my stomach
and eat an Asai Bowl.
Are you Assai?   Yes
.  Or an avocado toast outfit check,
please.  Wow, that's such a terrible outfit.
So, I'm wearing my water shoes,
[laughter]
because you gotta be safe in the water.  Then
my skirt panties from Berschka and this
is an all-around top from Poland Bear, it
's dark blue.  We bought this bag
for €4.50.  I think they're cool.
Put my cap on.
That's awesome.
Because of my head, because it's
already red. No, it's not red on you, but it is on
me.  I only have
sunburn on my back.  Simply from here.  Look, I
have sunburn, and look at my new
glasses! Because Jul wanted to buy jewelry,
I spent €70.
Yes, exactly.  It's my fault.  Look at
my other one.
Wait, wait.  No, it's about
mine.  My other pair of glasses.
You have to buy it.
Yes, that needs to be checked.
I must look a little like a
fly.   Yes
.  Oh my God.
Ah, I think that's totally cool.  But I have
n't worn them yet
because I just think they're a whole lot cooler.
But we're having a boot session today.
Maybe I should wear that one, because it's more
important to me afterwards.  A
windstorm hits and she falls into the water, and
nobody helps me get her.  You can
jump in after it.
Yes, I don't want to.
These are Mafit trousers by Julia
Motorx.
Somehow, nobody ever seems to know about it.  I'm
always the one being asked.
I'm right, you're a Motorola.
I discovered that at some point.
But that's where those famous jeans come from
, right?
Yes, I don't know.  I'm always
asked where my things are from.  Only
if they are from Model Rock.  And
then people always write to me: "Ha,
I don't know that at all."  My T-shirt
is from Brandy Melv.  I really have no idea what my bag is like
[laughter]
.  Wait, where is she from?  It
's definitely from Zalando.  [ __ ],
I really don't know.
And my flip-flops are from Crocs.  My
sunglasses are from some Ak brand
.
Ak bede, a Danish brand.  And Jul braided her hair
into two little braids.  Yay!
Here is our mobile.  for last day
and today.
True.  Drop Grandpa off tomorrow.
No, I have to hand it in today.  Please
hand it in tomorrow morning at 11 a.m.  It's always
24 hours.  Picked it up yesterday at 11.  It's
day two.
Oh, so this is my first time
riding a scooter.
Yes, Jana had simply never been
on a scooter before in her life, so she sat
on a scooter because we were
never allowed to, and I heard that
because it was dangerous.
Hello, it's being portrayed to me as if
I'm some kind of antisocial person who does
n't listen to her parents, but I'm
27 and you're 18, my you.   Yes
.  Hey,
I don't mean that from now on.  Yes,
but you spoke as if only
you were being heard.
You definitely rode a scooter before you were 18,
I swear.  No,
Fredi.
Oh right.  Yes, but I was allowed to do that
until her accident.  Then I was
n't allowed to anymore.
Yes, that's probably why I'm not allowed to, because of her
.
Yes, but I was
never allowed to have one myself.
Yes, that's what I wanted to say too, but this was
really the first time I'd
traveled alone in Thailand.  I was 18 then.
No, not in Thailand.  We did
n't go there.  That's
okay too.   What
was that?   Just
wanted to annoy you for a little while.
Now the journey begins.
Everything looks so much nicer through
my sunglasses.  Yeah, Diger, that's what I've
said for the 15,000th time now.
That's really crazy.  Every time
we drive somewhere, I think
I want to say, oh my God, Jana,
look how beautiful.  And then I look
outside of my sunglasses and then
I realize, oh, it's still beautiful.
Yes, of course.  But now mine is my
sunglasses.  Now there's also
a brown filter.   Ah
yes.  Well then, I'll say it now.
Awesome.  Stop.
Ah, we have to go back.  I left the
camera cap here.
That's the shop.  And do you see anything?   There
's a queue in front of it.  But
the queue isn't that long.  That
's five people.  We have now
decided to
go to a different one.  We were here yesterday for
coffee and they also have a coffee shop.
And do you think it's a snake?  Oh, I actually think that's really stupid
, because there are
snakes at both of them, but Julia wanted to be
Julia now.
That's much worse.  After waiting in line for 40 minutes,
we finally made it and
Julia is now eager to try on the skirt
.
Yes, because I didn't want to
wait for everything.  Jana wanted the W for that reason.
Hello.
It's just as delicious as
it looks, but you know exactly how it
tastes.  Do you get it?
Yes, I want one too.   It
looks a bit more intense than it
tastes.  Do you get it?  It tastes
amazing, but it looks even more amazing
.  It doesn't taste as flaky as
it looks.  Yes, more like a
milk roll.  Yes, so awesome.
OK.  Food is here.  OMG.
That was a mega successful
breakfast sport.   It's
12:30 pm.  We actually wanted to
leave at 12 o'clock,
because how long do we have to go now?  40
minutes of scooter riding?  So, actually, 36 minutes
by car.  But we have a
scooter that only goes 50.
Yeah, let's see, shall we?
Yes, but we're coming, it says we'll arrive at
1:05 pm or so
and the
meeting point is at 1:20 pm.  No, 1:10 PM.
Oh yes, my God.  Yeah,
let's go, right?
Guys, we're stranded.  [laughter]
Verche,
either he's out of tank, but
it says
full, but that can't be right
, because we've already
driven a really long way.  So it's currently empty,
that's why it's standing empty, but
yes.  Oh, I wasn't paying attention
.
Yeah, that's really awesome, because we're in the middle of,
I don't know, where.   The
tank is empty.  The scooter
tricked us.  Yes, the scooter says it's still
full.  I mean, I
knew it wouldn't be full anymore
, but normally with
scooters like that, the fuel level
drops rapidly at some point, but this one still
says it's full, so it
's such a
rip-off.  And now, um, the guy said
no gas because he heard the sound.
Yes, they're coming and bringing us a
new bike, she said, or we'll
get a new one, which makes me think, h,
if only the tank is empty,
just bring G with you.  But whatever.  Um, I'm
just wondering if they're going to pick us up now
,
and then we have to drive back,
or what the point of all this is.
No, they're coming together now, two of them.
No, wait a minute, that's right.  That makes absolutely
no sense.
That makes absolutely no sense.  Just give us some
fresh gasoline.
How are they supposed to get him out of here?
Yes, exactly, that makes absolutely no sense.
But he says it will take half an
hour.
No longer than half an hour.
Yes, supposedly no longer than half an hour
, but definitely half an hour,
and it's 1 p.m. and
our tour starts in half an hour.  So I
guess we don't have to go,
but can we? Can't you
call the tour operator and say if we
want to take the next one?  Guys, we were
rescued and we're getting a role.  Yay!  I
think we've been waiting for about 40 minutes now
, right?   Yes
.  Yes, longer, I think.  50.
Hooray!  We've finally arrived
in Portimao.  So far, I think it
looks really strange here,
but it can't actually be true.  I
think I'm in the wrong place here.
Yes, because it's actually a very well-
known place, but we
definitely have an awesome
Christmas market now.
Found a Christmas market supermarket.  We're going to get
something to drink and a snack now.
The tour lasts half an hour, starting 20 minutes
before the start.  So,
Fris Fr, that's great,
but not the fruit I want.
I would like a banana.  But they're
all bright green.
Should I eat them?  "Se jetzt wieder aus" (which is now
out again) wasn't really as great as
it looked from the outside.
I'm not really sharing any of those
, because I've already
eaten them, because I know them from Faula, who
is a Brazilian [ __ ].
Ah, I know those too.
H, I ate those in LA during filming
.  E,
because they already have the Portuguese training
controller.
They ordered Portuguese there.  That
makes sense,
but it's more cheesy than I thought.
Yeah, they're so awesome
.
They taste like they're just made of
rubbery cheese.
Yes, that's not it either.
No, it does have dough, but
I don't think you can really eat more than half of it.  Have fun with your
three.  Not me.  I got myself another
banana.
Yes, ice cream.
Ice.  We still have Mixberry,
water, and Pepsi, which I'm now
taking out.  I just need to quickly take some trash with me
.  Oh my god, I've spilled everything all over myself
.  I'm
completely full here too.  My hands are
completely full.  My arm is
completely full too.
Yes, I'm full of chocolate.   Didn't
you finish it at all?
No, it was so tattered
.  So, this one, I had an
ice cream that was a sandwich ice cream.
Oh my God, you can't take me
seriously.  Oh, wait a minute.  Is that
a pimple or is it chocolate?  Pimple.
Oh right.  Well then.  It was a
sandwich cheese, and the waffle part of it
was so soggy and
disgusting.  I think this ice cream was old.
Could
from the little
boy, it tastes just the same.
Wow.
Just a little bit of, uh, K went off.
Oh
yes.  No, I have a hair in my
armpit.
We are
not alone.  So funny.  There are so
many people here.  Oh, I feel like
I just
applied new lotion.  This is really not
great at all.  The journey begins.
[music]
[music] The
tour is over.  And where did we
end up?  At the shopping center.  But
that's Julia's fault, because Julia wants to go
to Sephora, right?   Is it
still allowed?  No, I've just gotten so tired because of it
.  Please pass
me the fruits.  Jul needed a
little Weidz, there wasn't a
brand he wanted.   There was
nothing [music] I
wanted.  Then I have to go and
buy it in Germany now, because
I think they
already have it there.  Well, anyway, I
bought some Mini Leaf in conditioner
for my crusty hair.  Once from Fenty
Hair in mini, and then I wanted to
try this one too, because I put it on
earlier and
Loki made
my hair so soft now.  So he did what
he was supposed to do.  I wanted to
try the other one too, so
I bought a Beautyblender.  I haven't had a
Beautyblender for years
and now I'm...  That was really
great!  60 € er.  Here comes the woman
with the good, important things.
Hello.  Oh my God, great.  Grazia.
Great.  I'm thrilled.  It's a good thing we
waited.  The problem is, they
simply didn't have the
opportunity to take our order earlier
, because let's just
start again.  Treasure.  Yes, but they could
n't have known when we could pay
.  The cash register was somehow broken,
and we waited patiently.  Yes,
it smells kind of like that.  So
you can't smell anything at all.
Yeah,
but I'd like some salt.  How do I
actually hold my Oh yes, soy,
because she gets it in such a way that she
can use it now, but doesn't have to get up?  It has to
be.  Yes,
then it's practical.  Acrobat (
partially)  No.  No.  No.
Why?
Well, it doesn't taste like it does in Thailand.   Does it
taste different in Thailand,
but also better?
Dude, why am I holding my knife with such a
restricted bite and such
strain?
So, I don't get how people
can say tofu isn't awesome.   I
need to see how it's made
.  Maybe I've just gotten used to it by now
, but I also think that
nothing tastes
good, even chocolate.
It tastes like a sponge.  Mhm.  Oh,
that's awesome,
dude.  I'm so tired right now.  Why?  You've had
a tough, sunny day
.  Don't be so hard on yourself.
We're back.
Our scooter didn't let us down this time
.  That was nice.
Yes, thankfully.  Yes, we're going to go for another
lap in the pool now.  It's 6 PM.  48
and then we'll go
shower right away, get ready, then head to
the start.  Yes, right?
Yes, that was a question.   Yes
.   Do
you wear makeup too?
Wow, I don't know.  Just a Z Bock, but
maybe.
Okay, we're ready to go again.
Our pool session lasted about 2
minutes, then I didn't want to anymore
.  We didn't feel like putting on makeup
, so we just left it as it was
.  This is my
outfit.  My skirt is from Stradivarius.
My top is from Pepe Jeans, and the
same bag and flip-flops from before,
and Julia is very
cute today.
Have you ever seen anything like this before?
No.  That's crazy, actually, it's
different, but
I think the skirt is totally cute.
Yes, but I think that one still exists too
.  It's from Subde.  And the
top is from Berschka.   It
looks like a belly dancing skirt.
Yes, because the federal government has progressed this far
.  I also have it in white.   Real
?
H looks like I could.
[snorting]
We bought ourselves bracelets.
Then check online right away to see if it's
still available.
Show off your bracelet.
Oh right.
Wow.  Wait,
mine is pink.
I bought two bracelets.   This is one example
.
Um, these are three blue stones.  Then
I said, yes, that
's a bit creepy.
No, not at all
, those are the eyes of Mom,
Dad and Jana.  No,
sort of.  Have you read The Eye Hunter
?  Nah, whatever.
No.  [laughter]
And yes, that's what we've got
together,
the pink version.  I have the blue
version.   That just goes to show
who we are.
Yes, sort of.
And I also have two new ones,
except if you're looking at me right now
.
The first and third ones are new from the
left.
We actually wanted a beautiful
sunset, unfortunately we did
n't get one, but we can live with that
.   It
is.  Yes, but yesterday it was really
great, pink and blue, I was looking forward to
sunbathing.
Yes, but that was only for 10 minutes
yesterday.  And you see clouds.
This doesn't work with clouds.  Oh,
there's a... What do you actually call these people
?  How I make a statue.  Now
we're taking pictures on the bridge.  No,
we've just spotted a snake.
I was actually about to tell you
that we're experiencing the nightlife for the first time
and it's totally
packed here.   Yes
.  Why are they all looking at us like that?  They all just turned around
.  Yes,
guys, it's just a camera.
Uh, yeah, we're queuing up now, are
n't we?
No.
Oh, not a single part.
Okay, this is going to take a very long time, isn't it?
Never.  Look, that's 20 pizzas
. I'm not waiting for 20 pizzas.
The noodle shop is up ahead.  There's about
three times as much of a queue as when
we were there.  And that's why
my conclusion is that we've
already talked about the noodle shop, because you talk about it
so casually.  And now
we've talked about that.  Yes.  Oh no, that was
in my [context] when I made my TikTok
blog, that's why
I thought I'd already
told you.  We definitely went
to a pasta shop yesterday and the
queue was really long.  It's
doubled right now.   There
were two people ahead of us,
but it took a long time.
Yes, imagine now.
Yes, that's right.  Yes.  Yes, that's why my
conclusion is simple: we should
miss the Nightli again for the next few
days.
Okay, so only tomorrow.  Morning.
[laughter]
Food has arrived.  I got Julia to come to me
.
Yes, I wanted to eat pizza.  But I did
n't want to eat at either of the two shops.   Yes
.  No.  Admit it, she looked real.
Yes, they looked a bit rough, but I would have done it
for you.  Fun.
Wow.  You wouldn't have.
I wouldn't really be in the mood for Indian food,
but oh well.  I said three times that we
could still leave, but then she said
no.  It is beautiful.
I think we don't even need to
make a taste test, because it will be delicious anyway.
I don't know.
Oh, okay, then you do one.   It
's delicious, isn't it?
Yes, the one in Cologne is better, but it's
tasty.
Oh, okay.   A
little bit of fun. Oh, oh, it's the next
day.  We're going to have breakfast now, but
Julia is still on the phone.   Yes
, yes, that's possible.
[music]
We're out and about.
Oh my God.  Yes, you film really well.
Yes, I... Oh, I was so small... I
was so here.  Hello.   Um
, we just had breakfast.   Had breakfast
.  And now we are going to go
to the scooter.  Hey, it's so crazy, at
breakfast there's always this guy, what's his name again
?  The Man of the Birds.  Yeah, it's like, some
guy who's
just
standing there in his hunter outfit, and then he's wearing
a glove and there's a
bird sitting on the glove and
he's just chilling while having breakfast.  So he's just standing there
with this bird, and
I think he's booked by the hotel
or something.  That's so weird, because he's
just standing there.  He's just like that, he's
such an NPC, you know, I
always feel so sorry for him.  I'm guessing he was
probably booked there to
entertain us.
Yes, yes, that's his job too.
Yes, of course, but
nobody reacts to it, you know?  Just like that with
his bird, and on the one hand I find
it really awful that he
has that bird there.   Yes
.  On the other hand, I
also think, oh God, the poor guy, he's just standing there
and this hotel thinks, that
's a good idea, a guy with a
bird can really save the money.
It's so strange.  I don't understand this
whole situation,
I do
n't understand what's going on.  That's so weird.
We absolutely have to
return a scooter now, and J really wants to go back
to Black and White Coffee, where
we waited in line for so long yesterday, but they
have a separate shop for Sundays.
We'll take her there now.
Exactly.
H up.
Wow,
like a princess.
Now I've started what I wanted to get
.  No sunglasses either.
H, you don't have any either.
I don't have any either.
Do you have to close the door while
driving?
Guys, I swear, yesterday I had
no more eye discharge, right?
[laughter]
You don't understand the wind on it.  It
's sick.   Yes
, I think so.
No, but it's really sick.  Yes,
so you think you're
standing, you're even sitting behind me and
saying the wind is strong.  But if you
[laughter] say
yes, then it makes no difference.  That's
correct.
We have our position,
I have something that I probably find
very cute.
You really don't shy away from it.  Yes, you can feel
it.  And I have a green juice
and I'm going to find it incredibly disgusting.
Yes, it's simply apple apple.
Celery, glue.
First it says apple, then it says
cucumber, then it says celery.  That
means it's not a cucumber and you don't say "
try it first" or "say it," but do
n't react.
Wait, react.   Did
you respond?   Yes
.  [ __ ], I'm done with it, it was really
bad.  I'm scared.
So
the first second is great and then it's
delicious.
Oh, this is ten times worse than I
expected.
So yes, it tastes like cucumber juice,
but not sweet cucumber juice.
What exactly did you expect, [laughter]
boy?  The second ingredient
listed is
cucumber.
Oh, that's completely unacceptable.
Yes, I think I have.
That's disgusting.
I thought it would taste a bit more like
apple.  There are already two apples.
The first ingredient was apple, and the fourth was apple
again.   Yes
.   Yes
.   Why is
that? I don't know either.   Are they
stupid?  I thought it would be more
apple.  It tastes really good.  That says
legitimate
apple, cucumber, celery, apple lime.
Wow,
that's completely unacceptable.  Should I? I don't dare
.  Come in there now.  That's
not so bad.
No.
Wow, that works.  No, that's completely unacceptable
.
Oh man, I thought I was so
healthy
with my green juice, but it's
really not working at all.  No, I can't
drink that.   Do
you like drinking that?  Yes,
that will be super fun,
I don't.  I would say Jana still has K.
Yes,
let's go.  So guys, as you can see, I
'm in bikini gear.  I feel a
bit criminal right now because I'm
only wearing a bikini and walking through
these hotel corridors, but I'm so covered in
oil and sunscreen, I
really can't do this.  Well, anyway,
we just handed in the scooter, or I just handed it in
.
I just returned the scooter and
we got some water because Julia is
recording a podcast now.  Diger, I can't take it anymore
.  I swear, this path is
really getting going.
Because Julian is recording podcasts now, and
in that time I'm going to the pool and then
I'll chill there for a bit until she
's finished, and then we'll drive or
walk to the beach when the scooter isn't available anymore
.  That's really sad, because he was
really fun.  I can
not anymore.  What are you doing now
, man?  I just want to
eat my awesome pizza that's
sitting right here in front of me.  Yes, you can tell by her expression
.  She feels bad because I have to
wait until I can eat,
because our Instagram girl has to do her thing first
.  Hi.  Wow, H was even shot with lightning
.  What do we say now?  That
's good now.  Can we eat now?  Three
is spicy
, because that's how spicy it's supposed to be.
No, the other one should be that sharp.
But he also thinks so.
Yes, you still need to explain that to people
.
Yes, firstly, we are on Wow,
disrespectful.  We are where
we are, where we actually
wanted to be yesterday,
but the queue was extremely long.   It's
2 PM now, so it's
chill here.  It's still
crazy when it's full.  Yes, it's still full, but
we have my seat.
Yes, and there are two salamis and he
said to one of them, "Do
n't take it, it's too spicy."
You're too young a girl for that.
Margarita
is quite good.  Yeah, totally awesome.
It's missing something like basil or something.
Yes, for oregano or SAS.  You can't
have everything, right?  Oh my God, the
beads of sweat on your face say it
all.
Yes, please.  Okay, no harm done at all,
dude.  I
started filming way too late again.  Actually,
I wanted to film Julia
photographing a door, because we are
currently looking for doors for Julia, as
Julia has a great vision for her
story.  Do you want to introduce them?  I
've seen so many beautiful doors here,
I've photographed them and then
I want to
post lots of doors in a story, one after the other,
but I'm only at five so far.  Huh,
how much do you want?
My vision was 16. Well, not 16,
but
seriously.
No, more than that.  I thought about five.
No.  Oh, then we still have a lot ahead of
us.  I'll have to keep my eyes open even more
.
I think we shouldn't do it like this.
So, I'm saying everyone skips after the fourth door
.   Not at all
.  After the fourth door,
everyone slowly starts to realize this.  Yes.   Yes
.  OK.  You know, as you can see,
oh, here we are.  Hi.  Yes, we
already drove past it on
our scooter.
We shouldn't make this such an
aggressive task, you know?
Yes, but I enjoy it; it
should just happen that way.
OK.  Yes, we're definitely going to the
beach right now.  How much longer will we run
?
Allegedly 6 minutes.  [clears throat] Okay,
fine.
Last goal.
Yes, that's definitely the goal.  It
's really, really crowded here.
Wow, you're really in the mood right now.
Yes, that's definitely the goal.
[laughter]
Exactly.
I'm really hot.  I'm already lying down.  Yes,
then let's just go into the water now
.  Yes, okay.
After 20, 25.
Oh my God, now you know how
someone else always feels about you.
That's not true.  That's not true.
Swear to it.
Oh my God, we
finished at exactly the same time.  Yesterday, the day before yesterday.
Yesterday we didn't even get ready
.  This is a blatant lie.  Okay, let's
ask our parents.  Huh, Jew, I swear.
We used to always lie and say, "Oh my God,
this is so incredibly funny!"
So, outfit, my top is from
Hollar, my pants are from Pullen Bear,
my Favianos, my bag is from
Coach, my King is from H&M, Julia's
pants are from Berschka, her top is
from
Rate mal
Berschka,
no.  His outfit.
No, M Rocks.   Yes
.
Ah, [laughter]
the Flippies.
Flippies,
no idea.  Sleepers.  Oh, beautifully
dirty.  In bag.
I have solar bromo with beer.   Do
you see that?
Yes, I see that very clearly.
I don't think this is
sunburn, by the way.  This strange mark
on my leg.  Yes, we're taking
photos now and then we actually wanted to go out to
eat, but neither of us is that
hungry, so
not yet.  Yes, but we eat
Smashburgers, probably just
a Smashy given
.
Hi,
that's really awesome!  Wow, that looks
intense.  Wow,
I'm kind of impressed.
30apen
Thank you.   No idea
.
Test heard what he said.   Yummy
.  What did she just
give us?  The sauce without asking?  No,
it tastes a bit like
pickles.
Yeah, it's awesome.
Sun, no, Sun.
Oh my God.  Yes, I swear, I
just forgot.  We just
made a TikTok video and showed off some packs,
what else?
It was fake.   What
?  I said we
made a few photos and a video.  Oh, I see now
.  We just
made a TikTok video and it was fake.  No,
I said we have TikTok
and a few picks.  Oh right.  Everything's fine
guys, we're not faking it.  Luki, every
TikTok is fake.  Yes, I was just about to
say, actually
yes, it was fake.  Sorry guys, we're
fakers.
Every picture you intentionally post
is fake.
Yes, we are. I say,
but on the other hand, it's real because it's
not AI, one can say by now.
So it's really
great again.  What used to be fake is now
real, oh my god.
Thank you, AI.  Fun.
No,
bye AI, what am I even talking about
?
No,
there are now musicians on
TikTok who are completely AI,
who simply have insane voices
and can unfortunately convey really intense
emotions.  This is so
awful.   All
I ever see are these imitations of
Beyonce or whatever, these new songs
by her.  I don't even want to say who
it is, because then you'll look and then
save the songs on Spotify
and I'm really
giving Spotify,
boy.  Yes, that's a whole ass artist,
simply.  There
are also those Instagram accounts, like model
accounts or something.
But they're all absolutely terrible,
thankfully.  But this guy, he
simply doesn't exist, he has
a voice.  I get goosebumps.
Oh,
that's bad.
I find it amazing that voices can be
imitated better than
photos.  Yes, that's true, because you
can already do that, that's the thing,
normally we all
thought, yeah, as long as AI people and stuff
can't convey feelings and
stuff, and you realize that it's not
okay, but bro,
he makes me cry unfortunately.
Wow, I have the feeling you're exaggerating right now, so
listen.
No, I'll show you later.  I
blocked it because I didn't want to.  No,
I'm not going to do that, but I'll
show you and you'll be shocked,
and unfortunately, the song is also... No,
all the songs he has,
but they're self-written.
Yes, from AI, I guess.
Why not let AI
write for artists?
Well, because then the art is gone.   Yes
.  Yes, you realize that yourself
now.  Lol.  Fun,
fun.
Yes, we have to
work against it for as long as we still can,
huh?  Yes, K will eventually die out again
.  Diger, this AI
artist, already has 38,000 followers.
Yes, because it's a big thing right now,
but in about 10 years it will definitely be
boring.
No, I'm telling you, that's what we think now, yeah,
I'm not even saying that to them,
I'm just saying that these AIs
can convey human emotions and trigger something in us, will that bother
people eventually?
I hope
not, but I
have a feeling it will, no
longer whether the person on the screen
is real or not, because they do
n't know them anyway, you know?  It would
n't bother us in itself if we did
n't know why AI
is crap.  It's not just that it's awful, it
also generally replaces people,
it replaces art, and it replaces everything.
Yes, but I mean, if we did
n't consider that now, we wouldn't
care.
That's kind of a stupid argument coming
from me.   That
's a really stupid [laughter], not a "
I take it back" at all, guys.  Okay, but that
's the thing.  I thought, okay,
people know they're not real
people, so they're
not interested.  But I can't
imagine that the more normal this becomes, the
less it will bother people, because
they know them, since most people do
n't know us personally either.
Accordingly, for them,
at least when it comes to music and such, it makes
no difference whether it's a real
person or not.  As long as the
feelings are conveyed in the same way and
you feel like you have a connection
to this person.  Do you know what the
topic is?
Yes, I think that's totally muddy and shitty.
I find it totally muddy.  [laughter]
Yes, that's my contribution.
I thought about it.  That was really awful
.  That's all for now.  Ciao.
[laughter]